{
    "id": "6d580c06fef841c1a3a9161676b5d591",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She comes to our parties but she never invites us …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "again"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "83b6830d76ea47139c6df0da9f0ecb6c"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. I was a child we lived in Singapore.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "While",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fa63676e909e420eb4e9309ff13cbce5"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no room ……………….. the bus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a12e30e5dcc74a44afdcdc8936d8452b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t seen her ……………….. years.",
            "description": "Either in or for is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e9e363beb8f54867897088e238c95258"
        },
        {
            "question": "The work was very hard …………………, but I got used to it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "first",
                "at first"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "62b55947d1814cd7a7144a8431a9d385"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I …………………. twenty pounds lighter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e769276181bc4c7ba6c8584bb2ce9035"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Where is Susie?’ ‘She has ………………. to Bangkok.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been",
                "gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7a8c06b4f24d4f6e915993d420c73382"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your name comes …………………. mine in the alphabet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "in front of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e3b7ec0f1cec4b0e9961bf98ead65c8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can play all musical instruments ……………….. the piano.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "besides",
                "except"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "53e198d3deae4e9196e850bfee249e93"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ………………… five children in six years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bore",
                "born",
                "borne"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8af020afbd2f424d9aaba4b96aafc843"
        }
    ]
}